

Henrik Mjaaland

Computer Engineer

(1)

18 November 1993



Gamleveien 14, 4315 Sandnes, Rogaland



+47 90215974



http://github.com/henmja



henrikmjaaland@hotmail.com

About Me ———

I am a computer engineer from Sandnes, Norway. I live in Lura with my fiancÃľe. I have a bachelor degree in Computer Science, and I am currently working on a masters degree (also Computer Science). I have previously worked as a production operator, seller, gardener, and as a warehouse worker. Preesently, I am working as a control technician for Nærbø Kyllingslakt. There, the tasks are IT-related (f.ex. control the assembly lines). In my sparetime I like to run, lift, bike and play football. As a person I am outgoing, hard-working and honest.

MATLAB

Go

Javascript

PHP

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

since 2017	M.Sc. Computer Science	University of Stavanger
2014-2016	B.Sc. Computer Science	University of Stavanger

Sandnes VGS

Realfag

2009-2012 General Studies (Science)

Portfolio

Github.com/Henmja

Website

https://www.henrikmjaaland.com

Certificates

2012	Driver's License, Class B
2012	Forklift License, T1
2016	Boating License

Experience

Experien		
Current	Control Technician	Nærbø Kyllingslakt
Current	Freelancer	Mjaaland CS Freelancing
2017-18	Production Operator	Nortura Forus
2016	Gardener	Facility Services
2015	Warehouse Worker	Megaflis Forus
2013-14	Seller	Burger Pizza Companiet
2012	Warehouse Worker	REMA 1000 Distribusjon

References

References are given on demand.